First major movement of Tai Chi, we are here and we make the notochord wave.
We bring in all the mesodermic movement.
The notochord wave and below all the mesodermic movement.
Next, we focus on the brain.
1. Brain growth.
2. Cephalic flexion.
3. Cervical flexion.
4. Pontine flexion.
5. Telencephalization.
Movement of the kidneys. It's a movement of external rotation.
Now, we will do everything related to the bladder and uterus, and
then we'll return.
Peritoneum, right hand in front.
I take the loop here, I bring it toward my hepatic side.
The hand here descends and finishes the rotation like this.
Like this, I have the loop right in front of me.
It grows.
I pull this hand, I reach for the loop here, and bring it back to
my liver.
And then the hand here descends, rises, and this one descends to form the
terminal phase.